Okay, we are here in the Google Self Driving Car.
好的，我们在Google自驾车。
We're inside.
我们在里面。
It's obviously driving itself.
这显然是在驾驶自己。
And it's doing everything by itself.
它本身就是在做一切事情。
>> And I am here as a passenger.
\u003e\u003e我在这里是一名乘客。
I'm really hoping that Sebastian did a good job in training this,
我真的希望塞巴斯蒂安在训练中做得很好，
because he is not driving right now, and I-
因为他现在不开车，而我 -
>> I am not driving, it drives better than me.
\u003e\u003e我不开车，比我开车更好。
>> I am at the mercy of this car.
\u003e\u003e我受这辆车的摆布。
That's true, it does drive better than me.
这是事实，它确实比我强。
>> So why are we talking about self driving cars then?
\u003e\u003e那么我们为什么要谈论自驾车呢？
>> Why are we talking about self driving cars?
\u003e\u003e为什么我们在谈论自动驾驶汽车？
Well we're going to start by talking about supervised classification, and
那么我们将首先讨论监督分类，并且
self driving cars are one big supervised classification problem.
自驾车是一个很大的监督分类问题。
>> What does supervised mean?
\u003e\u003e监督什么意思？
>> Supervised means that you have a bunch of examples.
\u003e\u003e监督意味着你有一堆例子。
Where you know sort of the correct answer in those examples.
在这些例子中，你知道哪些是正确的答案。
So I know that you have example of this from the self driving cars.
所以我知道你有自动驾驶汽车的例子。
>> Yeah so I mean we, we train our car and
\u003e\u003e是的，我的意思是我们，我们训练我们的车和
we show the car what's the right behavior.
我们展示了汽车什么是正确的行为。
And we did the Autobahn challenge we would take it out for a spin and it would
我们做了高速公路的挑战，我们会把它拿出来做一个旋转，它会
very carefully watch us human drivers drive and would emulate our behavior.
非常仔细地观察我们人类的驱动力，并会模仿我们的行为。
>> And in fact, this is sort of how people learn to drive, right?
\u003e\u003e事实上，这就是人们学习驾驶的方式，对吧？
>> Yeah, I think so. When I was a child, I watched my parents drive.
\u003e\u003e是的，我认为是。
And they weren't really good drivers, but
他们并不是很好的车手，但是
I would still copy a lot of stuff from them.
我仍然会从他们那里复制很多东西。
>> Yeah, so it's kind of like,
\u003e\u003e是的，所以有点像，
in the way the humans drive by watching lots of examples.
通过观察大量的例子，人类驾驶的方式。
That's what computers do when they're doing machine learnings.
这就是计算机在做机器学习时所做的事情。
You give them lots of examples, and they start to figure out what's going on.
你给了他们很多例子，他们开始弄清楚发生了什么。
That's what we'll be learning about.
这就是我们将要学习的内容。
>> And it's totally true.
\u003e\u003e这完全正确。
In this unit, you're going to be learning about.
在这个单元中，你将会学习。
Machine learning, the same way we, we program steps on a car.
机器学习，就像我们一样，我们在汽车上编程步骤。
You're going to program data and, and
你将编程数据，和
test out whether you can make a car go fast and slow at the appropriate time.
测试你是否可以让汽车在适当的时候快速行驶。
Using machine learning supervised learning.
使用机器学习监督学习。
>> That's right. So
\u003e\u003e没错。
we're going to be looking at a really cool terrain classification problem that
我们将看到一个非常酷的地形分类问题
was very important for Stanley.
对斯坦利非常重要。
You want to introduce that?
你想介绍一下吗？
>> So, in Stanley's case, I was driving through the desert and
\u003e\u003e所以，在斯坦利的情况下，我正在沙漠中穿行
the desert terrain is, like, ruts.
沙漠的地形就像车辙。
And boredom can be very brutal.
无聊可能非常残酷。
So it you drive too fast, you are running the risk of flipping over and
所以它开得太快了，你正在冒着翻转的风险
destroying yourself.
摧毁你自己。
So one thing we've trained the car to do is to really slow down at
所以我们训练赛车要做的一件事就是真的放慢速度
the appropriate time.
适当的时间。
We did this not by writing little rules,
我们不是通过编写小规则来做到这一点，
we did it by us demonstrating to the car how we drive.
我们通过向车辆展示我们如何驾驶来做到这一点。
And it will just emulate us.
它只会模仿我们。
>> How many miles did you have to drive to train that.
\u003e\u003e您需要开车多少英里来训练。
>> Oh thousands of miles.
\u003e\u003e哦千里。
We spent thousands of miles everyday in the desert.
我们每天在沙漠中度过数千英里。
>> Wow. >> And it took quite a while for me to copy.
\u003e\u003e哇。
Smart. >> Your poor grad students.
聪明。
I can only imagine.
我只能想象。
>> Well, I was the guy who had the pizza for everybody, but, it was a great time
\u003e\u003e我是那个为每个人都准备披萨的人，但那是一段美好的时光
because it was no email, we just had the, us and the software.
因为它不是电子邮件，我们只有我们和软件。
And every time you got the software back it was very obvious.
每次你拿回软件都很明显。
The car would punish us.
这辆车会惩罚我们。
>> Oh, that sounds great.
\u003e\u003e哦，这听起来不错。
So, I think we should probably get started with that.
所以，我认为我们可能应该开始。
Let;s try out a few different supervised classification problems.
让我们尝试一些不同的监督分类问题。
>> Yeah, so the unit's all about supervised learning, so let's dig in.
\u003e\u003e是的，所以单位的所有关于监督学习，所以让我们深入挖掘。
>> Sounds great.
\u003e\u003e听起来不错。